entravision.com 2019-06-08

# Entravision · Privacy Policy

  1. INTRODUCTION

This website is owned or managed by Entravision Communications Corporation (hereinafter referred to as “Entravision”, the “Company”, “us”, “our”, or “we”) and is part of the Entravision family of companies, which includes quality entertainment brands such as broadcast and Internet radio stations and television stations as well as digital properties.

This Privacy Policy describes the types of information that we may collect from you or that you may provide when you visit and/or use services related to our website located at <http://www.entravision.com/> and any website owned or operated by us that links to this Privacy Policy (collectively, the “Website”) and our practices for collecting, using, maintaining, protecting, and disclosing that information.

This Privacy Policy applies to the services offered by Entravision, including this Entravision Website, Entravision mobile services and any other features, content, services, or applications offered from time to time by Entravision in connection with this Website (collectively, the “Services”).  This Privacy Policy does not apply to information collected by us offline or through any other means, including on any other website operated by Entravision that does not link to this Privacy Policy or operated by a third-party.

Entravision is committed to protecting your privacy.  We provide this Privacy Policy to explain the type of information we collect and also to inform you of the specific practices and guidelines that protect the security and confidentiality of your personal data.  Please read this Privacy Policy carefully.  Please note that this Privacy Policy is incorporated into our Terms of Use, which also applies when you visit or use Services related to our Website.  If any term in this Privacy Policy is unacceptable to you, please do not use the Website or provide any personal data.  By accessing or using this Website or the Services,  you signify your acknowledgment of this Privacy Policy and consent to our practices as described herein.

This Privacy Policy may change from time to time.  Visiting this Website or using our Services after we make any changes to this Privacy Policy will be considered to be an acceptance of and consent to those changes.  Please check this Privacy Policy periodically for updates. If Entravision materially changes its practices regarding collection or use of your personal data, your personal data will continue to be governed by the Privacy Policy under which it was collected unless you have been provided notice of, and have not objected to, the change.

  1. information we collect about you

We collect several types of information from and about users of our Website, which may include information defined as personal data or personally identifiable information under an applicable law (“Personal Data”).  For example, we may collect information such as your name, birth date, gender, county, zip code, e-mail address, telephone number, address, job title, company/organization name, current supplier status, social media credentials (including profiles when you subscribe to specific websites), and information related to inquiries and requests.  We also may collect information about the internet connection and equipment you use to access our Website.  As you navigate through the Website, we may automatically collect information such as your usage details, IP addresses, and information collected through cookies.

**_Information You Give to Us_.** The information we collect on or through our Website may include:

  * Information required to become a registered user of or have an active account on our Website, including your e-mail address, screen name, username, and password. Entravision is not liable for any loss that you may incur as a result of someone else using your password or account, either with or without your knowledge.  You will not use the account, screenname, username, or password of another registered user at any time or to disclose your password to any third party.  You are solely responsible for any and all use of your account.
  * Information you voluntarily provide when submitting an order form or other request to receive information, products, or Services on our Website or a third party website or platform. The order form will ask you to give us contact information (like name or email address), financial information (like account or credit card numbers), and demographic information (like zip code or age).
  * Information you submit to us when/if you get in touch with our customer service, technical, or legal team, or any other employee at Entravision, via contact form, email, chat or through other means.
  * Information you provide when you download any software or application made available to view and/or download in connection with Services that is owned or controlled by Entravision and/or its licensors, affiliates and suppliers.
  * Information you provide us for registering for or using any of our Services.
  * Information that you provide by filling in forms and applications on our Website including your user name, password, your name, birth date, gender, county, zip code, e-mail address, telephone number, address, job title, company/organization name, current supplier status, social media credentials (including profiles when you subscribe to specific websites), and information related to inquiries and requests.
  * Information you submit to us when participating in a user-content generating initiative, such as an article, story, script, fan fiction, characters, drawings, information, suggestions, or concepts.
  * Information you provide if you choose to participate in our sweepstakes, contests, games, and surveys or because you want us to furnish you with products, Services, newsletters, or information, or in connection with content or suggestions you submit to Entravision for review, such as your user name, password, your name, birth date, gender, county, zip code, e-mail address, telephone number, address, job title, company/organization name, current supplier status, social media credentials (including profiles when you subscribe to specific websites), and information related to inquiries and requests.
  * Any information you provide when interacting with one of our Services, including participating or communicating in any public chat rooms, blogs, forums, message boards, news groups, or any form of communication in connection with this Website. Please note that submitting an online comment is public and generally accessible to, and may be collected and used by, third parties.  Entravision is not liable for the distribution of your Personal Data that is put on a public forum.
  * When you apply for career opportunities through the Website. If you choose to apply online with Entravision, Entravision will collect any Personal Data provided in your application materials, for the purposes of reviewing and responding to your application, if appropriate.
  * Information you provide when signing up for newsletters and other types of informational material when you inquire about products, technical support, and customer service; and when you provide feedback about our Website.
  * Records and copies of your correspondence with us (including e-mail addresses).
  * Information that you provide us by voluntarily conducting an online survey, contest or sweepstakes. These activities may ask you for contact information (like name or email address) and demographic information (like zip code or age).

If you give us the Personal Data of a third party, you represent that you have provided notice to, and received authorization to provide such information from, that third party.

**_Information We Collect About You_**.  As with many other websites, as you navigate through and interact with our Website, we may use automatic data collection technologies to collect certain information about your equipment, browsing actions, and patterns, including:

  * Information about your computer and internet connection, including your IP address, operating system, host domain, and browser type.
  * Details of your visits to our Website, including the resources that you access and use on our Website, traffic data, location data, logs, language, date and time of access, frequency, and other communication data.
  * Details of referring websites (URL).

The information we collect automatically is statistical data that helps us improve our Website and deliver a better and more personalized service, including by enabling us to:

  * Determine Website traffic patterns.
  * Count web visits.
  * Manage and improve the Services.
  * Track usage.
  * Security and monitoring purposes.
  * Determine traffic sources so we can measure and improve the performance of our Website.
  * Help us to know which pages and content are the most and least popular.
  * Observe Website search patterns to provide more intuitive navigation cues.
  * Determine the frequency of user visits and last date of visit.

We may share this information, and other non-Personal Data, with advertisers or other third parties that are not part of the Entravision family on an aggregate or other basis that does not disclose your identity or contact information.

  * how we use your information

Entravision will only use your Personal Data you provide in a manner that is consistent with this Privacy Policy.  If Entravision obtains Personal Data from a third party, such as a business partner, our use of that information is also governed by this Privacy Policy.  To enhance Entravision’s ability to tailor this Entravision Website to your preferences, we may combine information that you provide us on registration and other online sign-up forms with other information about you that we may obtain.

Below please find information about how we process information collected about you (including Personal Data). We may process information about you, including Personal Data, where the processing is:

  * Necessary to personalize your experience. We may use the Personal Data you give us to better tailor your Website experience to your interests, and to send you information about Entravision and its Services as well as promotional material on behalf of some of our partners.  We use other information, including Personal Data, that you provide to us to show you content in which you may be interested and to display the content according to your preferences.  We will also share this information within the Entravision family in order to enhance your experience on this Website and other Entravision websites.
  * Necessary to provide access to certain features on the Website and receive information suited to their interests. For example, a registered user is eligible for additional Services provided by this Website such as listener clubs and personalized content.  Our registration and special Services sign-up forms may ask you for contact information (like name or email address) and demographic information (like zip code or age).  You must provide that information in order to receive the benefits of registration or of the special Service.
  * Necessary to charge you for products and Services that you request. By giving us your credit card and related personal information, you are authorizing our store to give that information to the merchant and credit card company in order to confirm and fulfill your order. We will use contact information from the order form to fulfill your orders.  We may also use contact data to get in touch with you when necessary.  We will not otherwise use or distribute your financial information without your prior approval.
  * Necessary to contact you with information about the Entravision family and promotional material on behalf of some of our partners, and to contact you when necessary.
  * Necessary to administer our Website, help diagnose problems with our servers, to analyze trends, to track users’ webpage movements, to help identify you and your shopping cart, and to gather broad demographic information for aggregate use.
  * Necessary for us to comply with a legal obligation.
  * Necessary for entering into or the performance of a contract with you. For example: 
    * To carry out our obligations arising from any contracts entered into between you and us.
    * To provide you with the information, products, and Services that you request from us.
    * To process your supplier application and registration form, and to create online accounts for your organization and its authorized agents.
    * To communicate with you about our contracts or your account.
  * Necessary for the purposes of the legitimate interests pursued by a third party or us (to the extent it does not infringe on any data subject’s fundamental rights and freedoms). For example: 
    * To make sure that content from our Website is presented in the most effective manner for you and for your computer.
    * To allow you to participate in interactive features of our Website and Services (when you so choose).
    * To keep our Website safe and secure (for example, security protection and fraud prevention).
    * To provide you with technical support and to improve our Website and Services.
    * To provide you with information that you have requested and respond to your inquiries.
    * To notify you about changes to our Services or our Website.
    * To manage our everyday business needs, such as auditing, administration of our Services, analytics, and the enforcement of any corporate reporting obligations, or other policies.

  * Necessary to investigate and enforce, if necessary, a user’s legal requests, including, but not limited to, potential copyright or intellectual property infringements.
  * Pursuant to valid consent provided by you, in order to provide you with information about goods or Services we feel may interest you. If you do not want us to use your Personal Data in this way, simply do not opt-in when we ask for your consent on the relevant forms where we collect your data.
  * Allowed for any other purpose where you have provided valid consent where it is legally required.

  1. disclosure of your information

We may disclose aggregated information about our users, and information that does not identify any individual, without restriction.  Anonymous click stream, number of page views calculated by web beacons, and aggregated demographic information may also be shared with Entravision’s advertisers and business partners.  Subject to applicable law and regulations, we may disclose Personal Data that we collect or you provide as described in this Privacy Policy:

  * When you provide any Personal Data to any of our “special relationships” that are not owned by Entravision. These special relationships may include “powered by” partners, business partners, sponsors, and co-branded sites (referred to here as “co-branded pages”).  These might include, for example, pages that share our name and that of another entity, such as TicketMaster.  You should look for a specific Privacy Policy on any such co-branded page.  Any Personal Data that you provide when signing up at one of those co-branded pages may be shared with our third party partner.  Check our partners’ websites for information regarding their privacy policies.
  * When you apply on this Website for a job, we may, in our sole discretion, forward the information you submit to our parent, subsidiaries and affiliates for legitimate business purposes.
  * Subject to applicable law and regulations, if this Entravision Website is sold to, or merges with, another company not owned by Entravision, you should expect that some or all of your Personal Data collected from this Website may be transferred, sold to, or assigned to the buyer/surviving company. If so, Entravision will seek to obligate the acquiring company to use any Personal Data transferred by this Entravision Website in a manner consistent with this Privacy Policy, but cannot guarantee that it will be able to impose that requirement or that the acquiring company will comply.
  * To companies that are affiliated with us, that is, are part of Entravision.
  * To advertisers and business partners that are not affiliated with Entravision, but would like to send you information about their products and services. For example, some of the companies who supply prizes for Entravision’s contests may have special offers or promotions that might be of interest to users of the Entravision Website.  We will not share your Personal Data with such third parties without your permission.
  * To perform tasks (such as order fulfillment and payment processing) required to complete purchases you make through Entravision. Entravision must disclose your credit card information with such third-parties to complete any payment transaction on our Website.
  * To third parties who assist us in operating our Website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential.
  * To comply with the law, enforce our Website policies, or protect our or others’ rights, property, or safety.
  * For any other purpose disclosed by us when you provide your information or with your consent when required by applicable law and regulations.
  * To enforce or apply our Terms of Use and/or other agreements, including for billing and payment collection purposes, or to protect the rights, property, or safety of Entravision or our customers, or others. This may include an exchange of information, including your Personal Data, to other companies and organizations for the purposes of fraud protection and credit risk reduction.
  * With outside contractors or agents who help us manage our information activities ( _e._ , message boards, sweepstakes administration, order fulfillment, statistical analyses, data processing), or with outside contractors, agents or sponsors who help us with administration, judging and prize fulfillment aspects of contest, promotions, and sweepstakes. These outside contractors, agents, or sponsors may only use your Personal Data to provide Entravision with a specific service and not for any other purpose without your consent.  Entravision may only provide your Personal Data to a third party in those instances where you have chosen to receive certain information and have been notified that the fulfillment of such a request requires the sharing of your Personal Data.
  * With third parties where you have chosen to receive certain information and have been notified that the fulfillment of such a request requires the sharing of your Personal Data.
  * With third parties who help us customize our advertising and marketing messages you receive on our Website, or may work with outside companies to do so. Your non-Personal Data may be shared with these companies so this customization can be accomplished.  Entravision prohibits these companies from sharing your information with any third party or from using it for any purpose other than targeting advertising.
  * To protect the safety or security of individuals, such as to: (i) protect or defend the legal rights of Entravision, its employees, agents or contractors (including enforcement of our agreements); (ii) protect the safety and security of users of the Website or members of the public including acting in urgent circumstances; (iii) or protect against fraud or for risk management purposes.
  * With third-parties regarding specific registration modules, like survey, contests or sweepstakes. We will post a conspicuous statement on the registration module to the effect that we will be sharing with third parties the Personal Data and information collected.
  * When necessary to support certain functions and features of our Website. For example, this may occur at a feature that enables you, via our Website, to ask questions of persons or entities that are not part of the Entravision family.  By responding to those features of the site, whether by email or direct entry of information on our Website, you are consenting to our transferring that information to such persons or entities.
  * To comply with the law or a legal process, such as a court order or any regulatory proceeding.
  * Non-personally identifiable visitor information and other aggregate information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

  1. JURISDICTION AND Cross-border transfers of personal data

The Website and Services are intended for use in North America and Latin America. The data that we collect from you will be transferred to, and stored and processed in, the United States.  Please note that the data protection and privacy laws of the United States may not be as protective as the laws in your country.

We will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that your data is treated securely and subject to appropriate safeguards in accordance with this Privacy Policy and applicable legislation.

  1. Choices about how we use and disclose your information

Entravision strives to provide you with choices regarding the Personal Data you provide us.  We have created mechanisms to provide you with the following control over your information:

  * Cookie Settings: If you do not wish for us to install cookies on your device for the purposes described above, you may change the settings on your browser to block or limit cookies. For more information, please see <http://www.aboutads.info/consumers>.  Please note that if you block or limit cookies, you may not be able to use all of the features of the Website.
  * **Do Not Track Signals:** We do not currently respond to “do not track” signals.
  * **Opt Out of Receiving Email Message:** This Entravision Website provides you the opportunity to opt-out of receiving email communications from us and our special relationship partners. To opt-out of receiving email communications, you: 
    * May use the unsubscribe link provided in promotional communications;
    * May modify your registered user information on our Website; or
    * May send an email to [webmaster@entravision.com](mailto:webmaster@entravision.com).
  * **Opt Out of Receiving Promotional Materials:** If you receive promotional materials from Entravision, and want to stop receiving such materials, click the unsubscribe link at the bottom of each promotional email.
  * data security

Entravision employs commercially reasonable security measures consistent with standard industry practice for information collected through this Website.  We believe that we have adequate security measures in place in our physical facilities to protect against the loss, misuse, or alteration of the information we collect on our Website.  We also use internal protections to limit access to users’ Personal Data to only those employees who need the information to perform a specific job.  You should be aware that the Internet is inherently susceptible to security failures beyond Entravision’s control, and you should keep this in mind when communicating any information.

  * third party links

This Entravision Website may contain links to websites operated by third parties.  Entravision does not monitor or control these sites and makes no representations regarding these links.  Entravision is not liable or responsible for the accuracy, completeness, timeliness, reliability or availability of any of the content uploaded, displayed, or distributed, or products or services available at these sites.  If you choose to access any third-party site, you do so at your own risk.  The presence of a link to a third-party site does not constitute or imply Entravision’s endorsement, sponsorship, or recommendation of the third party or of the content, products, or services contained on, or available through, that site.

  1. cookie Policy

This Entravision Website may use a standard technology called a “cookie” to collect information about how you use the Website.  Cookies are small bits of information that Entravision places on your computer.  Entravision uses the cookies to identify your Internet browser, store your preferences, and to determine whether you have installed the enabling software needed to access certain material on the Services.  Cookies also help our Website to recognize your computer’s browser as a previous visitor.  This information allows us to customize delivery of information.  We use cookies only to gather information as indicated in this Privacy Policy.  We may use cookies, for example:

  * To save and remember registration information or preferences that you may have set while browsing the Website.
  * To deliver content specific to your interests.
  * To save your password so you don’t have to re-enter it each time you visit our Website.

We may also use “session cookies” which helps us administer the Website.  The session cookie expires when you close your browser and does not retain any information about you after it expires.

Third-party advertisements displayed on the Services may also contain cookies set by Internet advertising companies or advertisers.  Entravision does not control these cookies and users of the Services should check the privacy policy of the Internet advertising company or advertiser to see whether and how it uses cookies.

You can program your computer to warn you each time a cookie is being sent, block third party cookies or block all cookies.  However, by blocking all cookies you may not have access to certain features on the Services.

This Entravision Website may be linked to Internet sites operated by other companies.  Some of these third-party sites may be co-branded with the Entravision logo or an affiliated entity, even though they are not operated or maintained by Entravision (for example, co-sponsored chat pages, or advertising sponsor pages).  The Entravision Website may also carry advertisements from other companies.  Entravision is not responsible for the privacy practices of websites operated by third parties that are linked to or integrated with the Entravision Website or for the privacy practices of third parties or Internet advertising companies.  Once you’ve left the Entravision Website by such a link or by clicking on an advertisement, you should check the applicable privacy policy of the third parties or advertiser website to determine how they will handle any Personal Data they collect from you.

Some of the advertisements that appear on Entravision are delivered to you by third party Internet advertising companies.  These companies utilize certain technologies to deliver advertisements and marketing messages and to collect anonymous information about your visit to or use of our Services, including information about the ads they display, via a cookie placed on your computer that reads your IP address.  To opt out of information collection by these companies, or to obtain information about the technologies they use or their own privacy policies, see their individual websites.

  1. Google analytics

Entravision uses Google Analytics, a web analytics service provided by Google, Inc. (“Google”).  Google Analytics uses cookies, which are text files placed on your computer, to help the Website analyze how users use the Website. The information generated by the cookie about your use of the Website will be transmitted to and stored by Google on servers in the United States. Google will use this information on behalf of us as the operator of the Website for the purpose of evaluating your use of the Website, compiling reports on Website activity for Website operators and providing them other services relating to Website activity and internet usage.  The data collected through these tools is not tied to any Personal Data about you.

In case IP anonymization is activated on the Website, your IP address will be truncated within the area of Member States of the European Union (“EU”) or other parties to the Agreement on the European Economic Area (“EEA”). Only in exceptional cases, will the whole IP address be first transferred to a Google server in the United States and truncated there. The IP anonymization is active on the Website. The IP address that your browser conveys within the scope of Google Analytics will not be associated with any other data held by Google. You may refuse the use of cookies by selecting the appropriate settings on your browser; however, please note that if you do this you may not be able to use the full functionality of the Website.

By using this Website, you expressly consent to the use of Google Analytics on your activities on this Website.   You also can opt-out from being tracked by Google Analytics with effect for the future by downloading and installing Google Analytics Opt-out Browser Add-on for your current web browser: (click here <https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=en-GB>).

  1. banner advertising

We may license ad-server software from another company to place banner advertising on our Website.  All of the data provided and generated by the ad-server software remains in our possession and no data is transferred to the licensor of the software.  This feature of our Website may, on occasion, set “cookies” on your computer.  Any information collected or stored by the ad-service or the cookies is treated in the same manner as other information as described in this statement.

  * children under the age of 16

Our Website is not intended for children under 16 years of age, and Entravision does not knowingly collect or use any Personal Data from children under the age of 16.  No one under the age of 16 may provide any information to or on the Website.  If we learn we have collected or received Personal Data from a child under the age of 16, we will delete that information.  If you believe we might have any information from or about a child under the age of 16, please contact us at [webmaster@entravision.com](mailto:webmaster@entravision.com).

  * California privacy rights

Under California Civil Code section 1798.83, California residents who have an established business relationship with us are entitled to ask us for a notice describing the types of Personal Data we have shared with third parties for those parties’ direct marketing purposes during the preceding calendar year.  That notice will identify the categories of information shared with third parties, the names and addresses of those third parties, and examples of the types of services or products marketed by those third parties.  If you are a California resident and would like to request a copy of this notice, please submit a written request to:

General Counsel  
c/o Legal Department  
Entravision Communications Corporation  
2425 Olympic Boulevard  
Suite 6000 West  
Santa Monica, CA 90404

  * revisions to our privacy policy

We reserve the right to change this Privacy Policy at any time.  Any changes we make will be posted on this page.  If we make material changes to how we treat your Personal Data, we will notify you by e-mail to the e-mail address provided by you or through a notice on the Website home page. The date of this Privacy Policy was last revised is identified at the top of the page.  You are responsible for periodically monitoring and reviewing any updates to this policy.  Your continued use of our Website after such amendments will be deemed your acknowledgement and consent of these changes to this Privacy Policy.

  1. contact information

Should you have any questions or concerns about this Privacy Policy and our privacy practices, you may contact us at [webmaster@entravision.com](mailto:webmaster@entravision.com) or direct all inquiries to:

General Counsel  
c/o Legal Department  
Entravision Communications Corporation  
2425 Olympic Boulevard  
Suite 6000 West  
Santa Monica, CA 90404
